

JIAJUN YU

Adelaide Australia | jiajunyu@yahoo.com | 0466 659 310 | LinkedIn | GitHub | Personal Blog

CAREER OBJECTIVE

An enthusiastic computer science penultimate student at the University of Adelaide with coding experience and a strong interest in research aims to tackle real-world problems with the best developers and engineers. Now actively applying internship in the 2022 Summer.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science (Advanced) | The University of Adelaide, Australia

Mar 2021 - Nov 2023

- Courses: Object Oriented Programming, Algorithm Design and Data Structures, Web and Database Computing, Computer Systems, Algorithm and Data Structures Analysis, Algebra and Calculus (Mathematics), Statistical Modelling and Inference
- GPA: 7.000 / 7.000 (High Distinction Average)

Foundation Studies Program | The University of Adelaide College, Australia

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

- Courses: English for Academic Purposes, Critical Thinking, Math Methods, Physics, Specialist Maths
- Grade: 97 / 100 (Overall Dux)

SKILLS

• Programming Languages Java SE | C++ | C # | C | Python | R | MATLAB | Visual Basic

• Web Development HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Vue.js | React.js | Node.js | AJAX | MySQL

Tools
 Git | Vim | Linux (Ubuntu) | Pandas | Matplotlib

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student Researcher | The University of Adelaide, Australia

Nov 2022 - Present

- Research Topic: Facilitate the use of code quality feedback tools for novice programmers
- Identify quantitative and qualitative ways to measure quality of authentic student submissions
- Improve Pylint and Hyperstyle to make them more friendly and relevant to code smells of novice programmers

Academic Tutor | JR Academy, Australia

Jul 2021 - Present

- Deliver content to enhance university students' understanding in relation to relevant concepts and theories
- Formulate plans to support academic, personal and professional development
- Learn to be more patient, persistent as well as humble and focus on the job at hand

PROJECTS

Socialah | Group Web Development Project | Node.js & MySQL

May 2022 – Jun 2022

- A social event planning web app that allows you to create events and ask friends to fill up their availability.
- Skills Gained: Database design | Familiar with web development process (CRUD) | Version control (Git) |
 Follow plans to perform tasks | Time management | Communicate effectively with group members | Work well in team environment | Work under tight deadlines and pressure
- Video Demo: <u>Socialah Video Demonstration (YouTube)</u>
- GitHub link: <u>Socialah GitHub Repository</u>

Research on utilising blockchains to improve data security | Individual Research Project

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

- The research improves data security by utilizing Blockchains, IPFS (Interplanetary File System), Merkle tree as well as a special approach to slicing raw data.
- Skills Gained: Independent learning | Review literature | Discuss research methods with others | Present research progress | Write reflection & research reports | Cope with stress | Time management
- GitHub link: Research on utilising blockchains to improve data security

What are the prevailing attributes of UFO | Individual Data Visualisation Project | Python

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021

- The research identifies and visualizes the characteristics of UFOs (Undefined Flying Objects) by analysing word frequencies of descriptions from eyewitnesses contained in a dataset of 134,421 records.
- Skills Gained: Search for information | Analyse and visualize large amounts of data by Python | Presentation skills | Write reflection & research reports | Communicate with professors, mentors and peers
- GitHub link: What are the prevailing attributes of UFO

OTHER AWARDS

Adelaide Summer Research Scholarship for 2022-2023	2022
• The University of Adelaide Executive Dean's Award for Academic Excellence	2022
 The University of Adelaide College High Achiever Progression Scholarship 	2021
 The University of Adelaide College Top Student in Overall Dux 	2021
 The University of Adelaide College Top Student in Critical Thinking 	2021
 The University of Adelaide College Top Student in English for Academic Purposes 	2021
The University of Adelaide College Top Student in Maths Methods	2021
The University of Adelaide College Top Student in Physics	2021
The University of Adelaide College Top Student in Specialist Maths	2021
The University of Adelaide College Academic Merit Scholarship	2020

VOLUNTEERING & EXTRA-CURRICULAR PROGRAM

Volunteer Tutor | Confucius Institute | The University of Adelaide, Australia

Mar 2021 - Jun 2021

- Teach and help non-native Chinese speakers in the university with language difficulties
- Build connections with a wide range of students from different faculties
- Boost communication, time management skills, and accountability

Global IQ Connect Program

Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

- Build and develop inter-cultural communication skills and cultural intelligence through 5-week workshops by engaging with other students of different culture backgrounds
- Skills Gained: Understand the role culture plays in interaction and communication | Develop openness for people from other cultural backgrounds | Gain confidence | Learn to embrace diversity | Teamwork skill

INTERESTS

Java Developing | Web Designing | Blog Writing | Learning New Tech Stack | Researching | Teaching | Running | Swimming | Table Tennis | Listening To Music | Singing | Hanging Out With Friends

REFEREES

- Yang Su | University of Adelaide | Lecturer | yang.su01@adelaide.edu.au
- Ian Wenas | University of Adelaide College | Lecturer | ian.wenas@adelaide.edu.au
- Jiazheng Lin | JR Academy | Marketing Specialist | <u>jiazhenglin03@gmail.com</u>